Wait.
Before we go in
I just want you
to know that...
I love you
and I had a great time
on our honeymoon
and I can't wait
to go in there
and spend the rest
of our life together.
You're really sticking
with the shell necklace, huh?
Hey, you're back!
Hey, sweetie. Hey.
Come on in!
Yeah, come on!
So how was
the honeymoon?
Oh, it was so much fun,
but the best part is
we met this incredible couple
on the flight back.
That was the best part?
Good honeymooning,
tiger.
No, they were really cool
and they were
on their honeymoon, too.
They're terrific,
and they live right
here in the city.
Yeah, can we go call them?
I want to call.
I'm sorry, we're
just kind of excited
'cause we finally
have a couple
to hang out with.
A couple?
Like two people?
Like one, two people?
This is different.
Greg and Jenny are
in a relationship.
Ugh, Greg and Jenny, ugh.
"Hi, Greg, I'm Chandler,
this is Monica.
"Hi, Monica, this is Jenny.
Hi, Jenny. Hi, Greg."
Listen, they are
really great.
If you just got
a chance to...
You know what?
Why don't you just
give us our souvenirs
and get the hell
out of here?
Yeah, we didn't get
a chance to...
You've got
to be kidding me!
We didn't get
anything for anyone.
Mm-hmm, yeah--
nice necklace.
That you can have.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Hi!
Hello.
Welcome home.
So, how was
the honeymoon?
It was great,
it was great.
But how about you?
I mean, you're
having a baby.
Oh, look, I have
a sonogram picture.
Oh, good.
Ross
it's got
your wavy black lines.
All right
so now that Ross knows,
can you tell us
how it happened?
I mean, when did it happen?
How many times
did it happen?
Monica, that's
not right.
Start with "where."
Okay. Well, it happened
about six weeks ago
and I had just gotten home
from work
and Ross was already there
because I guess he'd been
hanging out with Joey.
You're welcome, buddy.
Yeah, thanks.
And so, I had
a lot of work to do
and Ross, nice guy
that he is
offered
to help me out
and then we had a little wine,
we got to talking.
The next thing you know,
out of nowhere
Ross comes on to me.
Um, that's, that's
a little misleading.
What is?
The lie you just told.
That you came on to me?
There's the one.
But you did.
I mean, let's be honest.
Yes, let's.
You know what,
uh, it's not important.
What's important is that
we're having a baby.
it doesn't matter
who came on to who.
Whom.
That's right.
You know you
kissed me first.
W-what?! You were
begging me
to kiss you.
You, you, you were
sending me signals
all over the place.
I was sending you
signals?
Yeah.
Okay, anyone in
this room think
that I would actually
send Ross begging signals
please, show of hands.
You know what?
it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter
what people believe.
What matters
is what happened.
Okay. Well, so
these signals...
Ross, explain this
'cause maybe I need
to be more careful.
I mean, am I sending you
these signals right now?
You know what?
Rachel, just drop it.
No, please-- show me
how I begged you.
I can show you.
I have it on videotape.
It's an expression.
I can't believe
he taped the two
of them having sex.
Yeah.
You got to tell the girl
before you tape her.
Such a rookie mistake.
You know who has
a great video camera?
Greg and Jenny?
Do you still want
to call them?
I want to call them.
Let's call them.
Yeah, ask them
if they brought
their friends
any souvenirs.
Hello?
Eighth Street Deli?
Hey, hang up.
You get food poisoning
just talking to that place.
Uh, sorry.
Wrong number.
Here you go, babe.
Hello?
It's the deli again.
All right, I'll have a sandwich.
I don't think
this number's right.
( laughing )
What?
You got fake numbered.
People don't do that.
Oh, I think we do.
They gave us a fake number?
Why would they do that?
I don't know.
You were a delight
to talk to.
You asked those insightful,
great questions.
And you've never
been funnier.
I mean-- joke, joke,
joke, joke.
I mean,
you were a hoot.
You know what--
don't worry about it.
You still got me
and Phoebe.
Excuse me, I don't want
Greg and Jenny's rejects.
Rachel won't talk to me.
She won't even open the door.
Mm, I wonder why, pervert?
Okay, listen,
I am not a pervert.
That's like the pervert motto.
Yeah, they have you raise
your right hand
put your left hand down
your pants, and repeat that.
Look, filming Rachel
was not something
I planned.
Okay look, here's what happened
and Joey, you can back me up
on this.
All right, about a month
and a half ago
remember I came to you
with a problem?
Um, uh, a personal thing?
What personal thing?
About... about sex?
That I hadn't had sex in months.
Yeah, I knew what you
were talking about.
Hey.
Do you have a minute?
I'd like to talk to you
about something
I'm really uncomfortable
talking about.
Sure.
How about, uh, you
showering with your mom?
I actually had
a topic in mind.
I'm kind of going through
a dry spell... sex-wise.
Oh, for like, months?
Five, to be... lying. Six.
Six months?
Whoa, that's rough.
Well, I mean,
it's not all bad.
I'm learning
to appreciate
the, uh, smaller
things in life
like the sound of a bird...
and the color of the sky.
The sky's blue, Ross,
and I had sex yesterday.
Please help me.
I have a date tonight.
It has to go well, okay?
I'm scared for my health.
Okay, okay. Um, ooh,
oh, I got something.
Okay, it's this story
that I came up with.
Very romantic.
I swear, any woman that hears
it, they're like putty.
Really, well, then,
tell it to me.
Okay. Now you're going
to want to have sex
with me when you hear it
but you have to remember,
it is just the story.
I'll try to control myself.
Okay.
( clearing throat )
Years ago,
when I was backpacking
across Western Europe...
You were backpacking
across Western Europe?
Have a nice six more months,
Ross.
Okay, okay!
I'm sorry.
Please, please, you were
in Western Europe and...?
I was just outside
of Barcelona
hiking in the foothills
of Mount Tibidabo.
I was at the end
of this path
and I came
to a clearing
and there was a lake,
very secluded
and there were
tall trees all around.
It was dead silent,
gorgeous.
And across the lake
I saw a beautiful woman
bathing herself
but she was crying.
Why?
Mmm, this
is great wine.
It's from France.
In Europe.
Western Europe.
You know, um,
a few years ago
uh, actually
I was backpacking
across Western Europe.
Really?
Mm-hmm, wait.
It gets better.
Um, yeah, I was in,
um, Barcelona.
I studied for a year
in Barcelona.
Anyway, um, so I was,
um, I was hiking...
I love hiking.
Ahhh! That's great!
I was hiking along
the foothills
of Mount Tibidabo...
I think it's
Tiba-DAH-bo.
Okay, do you want
to tell the story?!
Whoa.
What are you doing here?
How'd your date go?
Great. I'm across the street
having sex with her right now.
Your story sucks!
Hey, look, if it didn't work
it's 'cause you
didn't tell it right.
Show me
how you did it.
No. No, I don't
want to.
How long since you've seen
a girl naked?
I was backpacking
across Western Europe...
No, I'm not feeling it.
I was just outside
of Barcelona, hiking...
No, no, Ross-- I'm not hot.
Are you hot?
It's been six months.
I'm always hot.
Well, you're not
selling the story.
It's like you don't believe it.
Look, I've got to go.
I've got a date.
But try this--
do what I do
when I'm preparing
for an audition, okay?
I'll set you up
with my video camera
and you can record yourself,
and see what you're doing wrong.
I'll try that.
All right, now...
you're all set up.
Just hit "record," all right?
Good luck.
Thanks.
And, hey, Joe, listen--
If you ever have any problems
with the ladies
you know
I'll help you out.
That means a lot
to me, man.
( sighs )
Hello.
Can I get you anything, huh?
Lens cleaner?
Your battery okay?
Rachel?
Oh, Ross.
Hi.
Thank God
you're here.
You have to help me.
Were you just talking
to yourself?
That's less embarrassing.
Yes, yes, I was.
So when she came in,
I got distracted
and totally forgot
about the camera.
It kept rolling
and recorded everything.
Yeah, we're going
to need to see that tape.
Yeah.
What a great idea.
That'll get Rachel
to forgive me.
You know what?
This is not fair to her.
Let's just forget the tape.
Thank you.
No.
You're right.
Joey, no.
Loud and clear.
I still don't get why
Greg and Jenny would give us
a fake number.
You know, if they knew
what they were doing
they probably
didn't give you
real names, either.
Okay, maybe people give out
fake numbers
but they don't give out
fake names.
Oh, yeah?
Hi, Ken Adams.
Nice to meet you.
Regina Phelangie.
I just don't get it.
We didn't do anything wrong.
MONICA:
I know.
Although, you did tell
an awful lot of jokes.
I thought you said
those jokes were funny.
Joke, joke, joke, joke.
Joke, joke, blah, blah.
Well, maybe it was
all of your questions.
What about my questions?
The sheer volume.
It was like flying
with the Riddler.
Oh, I'm sorry,
was that another joke?
Was that another question?
Hey, is Ross still here?
Uh, no, Rach, he's gone,
but listen--
he told us what happened
and it does, it sounds
like an honest mistake.
Oh, really?
Well, how would you like it
if I had sex with you
and I taped it?
Oh, forget it.
Oh, and there he is now,
the father of my child
the porn king
of the West Village.
Look, it was an accident, okay?
I feel bad that it happened
but I swear
I didn't even watch it.
Anyway... here.
I thought you might be
more comfortable
destroying it yourself.
Thank you.
ALL:
No! No! No! No!
What?
ALL:
You can't do it!
You don't want
to see this, do you?
Hell, yeah!
I am not going
to show you this.
No, not the sex part.
Just the stuff
leading up to it.
Forget it.
She's destroying it.
Okay, fine! Fine!
We'll just have to think
of some other way
to put the whole
"Who came on to who"
thing to rest.
Come on now, think!
Look, forget it,
Phoebe, okay?
It's Rachel's tape
and she can do whatever
she wants with it
and she wants to destroy it.
So, end of story.
I want to see it.
What?
Clearly you don't want
people to see this tape.
Now I don't want people
to see this tape either
but you so badly don't want
people to see it
that it makes me want
to see it, do you see?
Are we watching
the tape or not?!
I don't want people
to see it for your sake.
Oh, I don't believe you.
I think you don't want them
to see you begging me.
Rachel, please.
Ah, a little preview.
Fine.
Fine, but I want
the record to show
that I tried to take
the high road
because in about
five minutes
I'm going to be
saying... ( laughing )
Okay, here we go.
I'm so happy.
Oh, thank God
you're here, Ross.
I need you to help me.
Were you just talking
to yourself?
Yup, there I am.
( singsong ):
You're going
to get pregnant.
I screwed up so bad.
I told Monica
that I would stuff
and send all these
wedding invitations
like, weeks ago, and I...
You didn't do it?
I, I, I had put them
in my desk at work
and I completely forgot
about them until today.
ROSS:
See? Once you get
a rhythm going
this isn't hard at all.
Sweetie, sweetie,
it's okay.
Everybody made it
to the wedding. I'm fine.
Kind of hurting
my hand, though.
I know.
I cannot believe
that I did this
especially after Monica
just went
on and on and on about it.
"Okay, Rachel. Here are
the invitations, Rachel.
"Now be very careful, Rachel.
Please, drinking no liquids
around the invitations, Rachel."
Whoa, oh, oh, oh,
oh... oh, oh, oh...
Did you do it
on our invitations?
Not on the ones we sent out.
Oh, so, just the ones you gave
back to us and we had framed?
Can you believe
this is already
happening?
I mean, it seems
like yesterday
they just got engaged.
I know. Hey, remember
remember the night
they got engaged?
How you and I almost...
Oh, I remember
how we almost...
Do you think we
would have gone
through with it
you know, if we
hadn't gotten caught?
Do you think
we would have done it?
I mean, I...
I know I wanted to
I just wasn't sure
if you wanted to.
Oh, I wanted to.
So we...
we both wanted to.
Interesting.
Yeah.
Mm. Anyway, um...
probably worked out
for the best.
Yeah, sure.
Okay, in about ten seconds,
you're going to see him kiss me.
And in about five seconds,
you're going to see why.
Ross, did I ever
tell you
about the time that
I went backpacking
through Western Europe?
It was just outside Barcelona
in the foothills
of Mount Tibidabo.
Okay, get ready
to see some begging.
I'd been riding
a donkey all day.
Oh, you came on to Ross.
What?
Now I'm so happy.
What are you talking about?
You used the Europe story.
That's the magic story you use
when you want to have sex!
How do you know
about that story?!
about that story?
I heard it from my friend Irene,
who heard it from some guy.
Some guy!
No, no. She told me
that his name was Ken Adams.
Ken Adams!
( knocking )
Hi.
So, apparently, people are
familiar with the Europe story?
Yeah, listen, about that--
the whole "Who came on
to who" thing
really doesn't matter.
I mean, I think it would have
happened either way.
I mean, if you hadn't
initiated it
I know I would have.
It was an amazing night.
It was. It was
an amazing night.
Do you think
it looked amazing?
I, uh, I don't know.
I mean, I honestly
didn't watch it.
Yeah, me neither... yet.
Uh, that,
that may be weird.
Yeah, it would be
really weird.
Good luck.
Good luck to you.
Mind if I mute?
Oh, please.
Oh. There, there go
the clothes.
You are undressing
awfully quickly.
Six months, Rachel,
six months.
Right.
( both sigh )
Hey.
Huh.
We, we look pretty good.
I was going to say.
Whoa, nice tan.
Thank you.
I had just gone
to the beach
that weekend.
Ah.
Oh. Have you been
working out?
I had been working out.
Well, this is so much
better than I ever...
Oh.
Ew.
Oh, that's not pretty.
Oh. Oh. Oh, God.
Oh! Oh, no!
Oh, make it stop.
No, no!
Make it stop!
No!
Hello, Greg?
Hi, this is Monica
from the plane.
Listen, the number
that you gave me, 853-5...
That is their
old number!
Jenny's been giving it
out since they moved.
Jenny. That is so Jenny.
I know.
Hey, listen
how would you like
to get together
say, next Saturday?
Okay, how about Sunday?
Okay, um, the week
after that?
The week after that?
You know what, Greg?
You know what?
We are good, interesting,
funny people
with good questions
and if you and
your precious Jenny
can't see that, then...
January 15th?
We'll see you then.
[Captioned by
The Caption Center
WGBH Educational Foundation]